<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cards on PIG的记录日常</title>
    <link>https://dkturingfz.github.io/card/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cards on PIG的记录日常</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <atom:link href="https://dkturingfz.github.io/card/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Style</title>
      <link>https://dkturingfz.github.io/card/style/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dkturingfz.github.io/card/style/</guid>
      <description>王维青年时期有积极的人生态度和政治抱负，写成“陇西行”等一类关于边塞、游侠的诗篇，运用歌行的体裁，描写各方面的题材，具有岑参、高适那种雄浑的气派。 王维后期歌咏山水的作品，真正代表其诗歌艺术。作品以五言为主如《鸟鸣涧》，描写退隐生活、田园山水，追求清静闲适的精神生活，风格恬静清朴。</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://dkturingfz.github.io/card/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dkturingfz.github.io/card/projects/</guid>
      <description>Ten plays are attributed to Seneca, of which most likely eight were written by him. The plays stand in stark contrast to his philosophical works. With their intense emotions, and grim overall tone, the plays seem to represent the antithesis of Seneca&amp;rsquo;s Stoic beliefs. Up to the 16th century it was normal to distinguish between Seneca the moral philosopher and Seneca the dramatist as two separate people. Scholars have tried to spot certain Stoic themes: it is the uncontrolled passions that generate madness, ruination, and self-destruction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://dkturingfz.github.io/card/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dkturingfz.github.io/card/publications/</guid>
      <description>Works attributed to Seneca include a dozen philosophical essays, one hundred and twenty-four letters dealing with moral issues, nine tragedies, and a satire, the attribution of which is disputed. His authorship of Hercules on Oeta has also been questioned.
De Providentia (On providence) - addressed to Lucilius De Constantia Sapientis (On the Firmness of the Wise Person) - addressed to Serenus De Ira (On anger) – A study on the consequences and the control of anger - addressed to his brother Novatus Ad Marciam, De consolatione (To Marcia, On Consolation) – Consoles her on the death of her son De Vita Beata (On the Happy Life) - addressed to Gallio </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
